Guide to the Michael Johnson Papers, 1881-1995 05656
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission, 04
  - PA PUC v. Equitable Gas Company, 1985 (Box 16)
  - PA PUC v. Metropolitan Edison Company, 1985 (Box 17)
  - PA PUC v. National Fuel Gas Distribution Corporation, 1985 (Box 17)
  - PA PUC v. Pennsylvania Power Co. recommended decision, 1984 (Box 15)
  - PA PUC v. Philadelphia Electric Company, 1984 (Box 15)
  - PA PUC v. Philadelphia Electric Company, 1985 (Box 17)
  - PA PUC v. West Penn Power, 1985 (Box 17)
  - PA. Senate Bill 366, March 25, 1982 (Box 24)
  - PECO and Energy Education, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - PECO merchandising-jobbing-nuclear promotion, 1983-1985 (Box 13)
  - PECO Service Territory construction jobs, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PECO Supreme Court appeal, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Pennelec - docket sheets filed, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Pennsylvania Bulletin, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pennsylvania Electric Association statements, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Pennsylvania energy choices, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Pennsylvania Energy Primer, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Pennsylvania Energy Ratepayers Coalition recognition, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Utility Users, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Pennsylvania Power and Light Company, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Pennsylvania Utility Consumers' Conference, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Pennsylvania utility reports, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Personnel, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Personnel, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Personnel, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Personnel, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
  - Personnel, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Petition, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Philadelphia Area Industrial Energy Users Group.. .v. PECO, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Philadelphia Electric Co. news publications, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Philadelphia Electric Company v. PA PUC, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, July 31, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PP&L annual report, 1984 (Box 15)
  - PP&L long-term debt, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Procedures manual PA-PUC, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Public input hearings, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Public Interest News, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Public meeting order, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Public Power, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Public power-The Assembly State of New York, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Public Utility Law codification H. B. 489, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Public Utility Regulatory Reform.. .Arizona -Woodward, undated (Box 15)
  - PUC bill signing-photograph, 1976 (Box 5)
  - PUC legislative reform, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - PUC v. Metropolitan Edison Company, 1979 (Box 8)
  - PUC annual report, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - PUC historical overview-Kovach, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PUC v. Bell Telephone Company, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PUC v. Peoples Natural Gas Company, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PUC v. PECO Consolidated reproduced record, 1983 (Box 13)
  - PUC v. Philadelphia Electric Co.-Limerick, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Racine, Stephen, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Rail Safety, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Rate Case Handbook, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Rate case status and activity, 1984-1986 (Box 15)
  - Rate Cases Spreadsheets, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Rate Cases Summary, 1976-1985 (Box 20)
  - Rate Cases Summary (for Company by year & case no.), 1985 (Box 20)
  - Rate Shock: Confronting the Cost of Nuclear Power, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Reasonableness of the cost of Quarto Mine Coal, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Recommendations for dealing with payment troubled customers, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Recommendations for dealing with payment troubled customers response, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Regulations concerning utility advertising, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
  - Reporter, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Residential Energy Conservation Action Program, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Residential Utility Consumer Payment Problems Volume IV, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Residential Utility Consumer Payment Problems Volume V, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Residential Utility Consumer Payment Problems, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Rosenfeld testimony re energy efficiency, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Salary question, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Second Technical Education Conference, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Senate of Pensylvania Executive Calendar nominations, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Separating transportation from fixed utility regulation..., 1983 (Box 13)
  - Settlement agreements language, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Shapp-How to Improve the National Economy, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Shapp photograph and cards, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Shortway Suburban Lines application, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Startway Suburban Lines, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - State Congressional Profile, 1981 (Box 9)
  - State-local taxation of public utilities in Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Statement, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Statement before Consumer Affairs Committee-endorsements, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Statement-Bodnack, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Statement by Commissioner M. Johnson, undated (Box 24)
  - Statement of M. Johnson before the Senate Consumer Affairs Comm., November 13, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Statement on the PUC Sunset Legislation, December 18, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Statement re Limerick-Cawley, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Statement re Limerick-Johnson (draft), 1983 (Box 14)
  - Statement-Taliaferro, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Statements, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Statements, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Statements, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Statements by M. Johnson on various cases and companies, 1982-1983 (Box 24)
  - Stinchcomb tax cabs, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Suburban Bus Lines-briefs, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Suburban Bus Lines Hearings, 1962-1982 (Box 4)
  - Swearing-in Ceremony-photographs, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Taxi regulation-HB 1799, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Telephone messages, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Telephone messages, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Telephone Utility-management audit program and measurement criteria, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Testimony re Limerick Unit II, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Three Mile Island part 1, The New Yorker, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Three Mile Island statement, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Three-Mile Island: Who Pays the Bill? CRS report, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Title 66 Public Utilities, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Tock's Island, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Tock's Island article, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Tock's Island background, 1969-1975 (Box 4)
  - Tock's Island statement, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Toward a broad reading of mplied powers of state public utilities, 1985 (Box 16)
  - UGI company annual report, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Utilities summaries, 1982-1985 (Box 10)
  - Utility background brochures, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Utility Information - Quarterly Reports #315, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Utility Information - Quarterly Reports #329, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Utility rates summaries, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Various fun facts to know and learn, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Water company rate increases, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Water Utility-managmenet audit program and measurement criteria, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Werner Bus Lines, Inc., 1978 (Box 8)
  - West Penn Power, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Why the U.S. will not achieve energy self-sufficiency-Mcketta, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Zemprelli v. Thornburgh opinion, 1979 (Box 8)
- Health and Health Care Services Initiatives, 5
  - Action for Mental Health report, 1961 (Box 18)
  - American Family report, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
  - American Medical Association, 1960-1965 (Box 18)
  - Bartlett, F. Lewis articles, 1964-1968 (Box 18)
  - Bartlett, F. Lewis correspondence, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross Community Data report, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross Community Data report, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross (conflict of interest questionnaire), 1978-1984 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross Labor utilization report, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia Board of Directors, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia telephone directory, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia-aging, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia annual report, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia financial reports, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia financial reports, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia hospital agreement, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia management survey, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia-Markson address, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia-Markson address, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia People Page, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia People Page-Bilines, 1986 (Box 19)
  - California State hospitals, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Caron Institute, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Chit Chat Newsletter, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Death rates by occupation, 1934 (Box 18)
  - Deinstitutionalization and mental health services, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Growing controversy over putting mental patients 'on the street, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Health care alliance, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Health care alliance News, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Health care leads, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Health care legislation, 1959 (Box 18)
  - John Wanamaker Award speech, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Mail-Senate Bill 1369, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Medicare, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Mental health, 1960-1967 (Box 18)
  - Mental Health Law Project's Alert, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Mental Health Law Project's Alert, 1985 (Box 19)
  - News clippings, 1982 (Box 18)
  - News clippings, 1984 (Box 19)
  - PA House Bills 1141 and 1142, articles, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
  - Pennsylvania Blue Shield Preferred Provider Directory, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Pennsylvania Mental Health, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 18)
  - Personal Care Residence model, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Resume, undated (Box 19)
  - Richardson v. Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia No. 83-0493, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation annual report, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Saint Vincent Serenity Program, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Sheltered workshop study, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Sheltered workshops, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Souder v. Brennan report, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Statement of Morton Birnbaum to the Joint Comm. On Public Health and Welfare, undated (Box 25)
  - USDL advisory committee on sheltered workshops, 1969-1975 (Box 18)
  - USDL advisory committee on sheltered workshops, 1975 (Box 18)
  - USDL subcommittee on patient-worker regulations, 1975 (Box 18)
- Photographs, 06
  - Blue Cross Dinner, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Governor Schapp - M. Johnson & Sulamith Johnson, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Hill-McDevitt-Boher-Haletsky, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Johnson with Others, 1966 (Box 23)
  - Lewis Stevens Conference, 1966 (Box 23)
  - PA. AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 23)
  - PA. AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 22)
  - PA. AFL-CIO Convention, undated (Box 22)
  - Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association Meeting, 1967 (Box 23)
  - United Labor Council Award, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Voter Registration, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Woman, seated (negatives), undated (Box 23)